LIDOR ELIYAHU SHELEF

HA-ALMOG STREET • MAALE ADOMIM

+972 527222495 • IVANLIDOR98@GMAIL.COM

https://www.linkedin.com/in/lidor-e-s/ • https://github.com/LidorPrototype

OBJECTIVE

Software Engineering student and a Data Scientist, with experience in object-oriented programming, data science, android and flutter development and Machine/Deep Learning. Responsible, team player, quick learner and able to take on individual projects from zero.

EDUCATION

Azrieli College of Engineering Jerusalem

2019 - Present

• B.Sc. Software Engineering student

ONLINE COURSES

- Machine Learning Scientist with Python: https://www.datacamp.com/tracks/machine-learning-scientist-with-python
- Databricks Machine Learning Engineer Learning Path
- Deep Learning with PyTorch by Facebook AI: https://www.udacity.com/course/deep-learning-pytorch--ud188

COMPUTER PROGRAMMING SKILLS

Programming Languages

- Proficient in: Python, Java, Flutter, C#
- Familiar with: SQL, C, C++, JavaScript, Ruby

Software

- Workspaces: Android Studio, Anaconda, Visual Studio Code, Eclipse, Unity, Bluel, PyCharm
- Platforms and Frameworks: Azure, Databricks, Firebase, Apache Airflow, FastAPI
- Operating Systems: Windows, Linux, macOS

PERSONAL COMMERCIAL PROJECTS

- AutoScraper: automatic web scraping to collect data for ML projects, using Requests, BeautifulSoup and Scrapy
- Virtual Assistants and chatbots with Python: https://github.com/LidorPrototype/Chatbot-Virtual-Assistant
- Applications I created: https://play.google.com/store/apps/dev?id=6589420104492859272
- Online Portfolio Project: https://lidorprototype.github.io/

WORK EXPERIENCE

Bank of Israel - Data Scientist

2021 - Present

Leading, programing (with Python), and scheduling (via Airflow) Data Science processes:

- Data Collection, Data Storage, Visualization, Data Analysis and Dashboards Programing
- Developing Machine Learning Models (Scikit-Learn, Keras, TensorFlow, Neural Networks, NLP algorithms etc.)

Shaare-Tzedek Hospital - Security guard

2018 - 2021

- Hospital patrols and maintaining order and organization
- In charge of all entrances of the hospital as well as looking for potential suspects and threats

Dan Jerusalem Hotel - Security guard, Shift Manager

2017 - 2018

MILITARY SERVICE

Artillery brigade, achieving the rank of Staff Sgt.

2013 - 2016

- Technological systems called "Gabrili" and a Muzzle velocity meter
- Responsible for directing Self-propelled gun shell fire
- Combat Training in high intense situation

VOLUNTEERING

The IMACT! Scholarship for Fighter Soldiers of the IDF

2018 - Present

- The Wellbeing for The Holocaust Survivors organization
 - Helping with everyday errands.
 - Assisting with smartphone/pc features and communicating programs

LANGUAGES: Hebrew - native • English – fluent